American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1K: State Correspondents, 1930-1969; 44 boxes
    - District of Columbia: Galardi - Disloyalty Discharge, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia: Jordon, Thomas murder case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia: Legislation Conference with Congressmen, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia: Marzani - Bail Case relating to indictment for being communist, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia: Parole for wartime offenders, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia: Restrictive covenant case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia: Tunsell- African American Trainmen's Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 12)
    - Florida, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 13)
    - Georgia, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 14)
    - Illinois: Brundage-Union Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 15)
    - Illinois: Heirans Sodium Penthothal Case - drug induced confessions, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 16)
    - Illinois: Colegrove, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 17)
    - Illinois: McNabb Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 18)
    - Illinois: Montgomery Ward Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 19)
    - Illinois: Restrictive Covenant Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 20)
    - Indiana: Seals - Barber License Law Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 21)
    - Illinois: State Employees' Loyalty Oath, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 22)
    - Iowa: Coppock, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 23)
    - Iowa: Parochial School Bus Transportation, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 24)
    - Kansas, Kentucky and Louisiana, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 25)
    - Maine: Pine Tree Tavern Student Discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 26)
    - Maryland: Mendelez Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts: Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 29)
    - Michigan, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 30)
    - Michigan: Bob-Lo Excursion Co. Discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 31)
    - Michigan: Callahan Foreign Agents Registration Act, 1947; 1 folder (Box 559, Folder 32)
    - Michigan: Krein Union Trial, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 1)
    - Michigan: McLean, George Habeas Corpus Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota: Cleary, James, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota: McLean, Clarence Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota: Rediker, Randolph, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 6)
    - Mississippi: Dixon Army Discharge, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 7)
    - Mississippi: Lewis and Trundell Execution Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 8)
    - Mississippi: White, Howard Death Sentence Theft case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 9)
    - Missouri: Married women teacher's case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 10)
    - Missouri: Restrictive Covenant Cases, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 11)
    - Nebraska: Hawk, Henry Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 12)
    - Nevada: Williams, Henry Police Brutality, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 13)
    - New Hampshire, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 14)
    - New Jersey, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey: ACLU Newark Meeting, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 16)
    - New Jersey: Ambruster, Howard, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 17)
    - New Jersey: Bower, Susan, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 18)
    - New Jersey: Chiropractors Licenses, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 19)
    - New Jersey: Constitutional Convention, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey: Johnson - Blue Ribbon Jury Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 560, Folder 21)
    - New Jersey: Longo, John - Jury selection, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey: Nelson, Rudolph, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - New Jersey: Passaic Valley Water Commission - discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey: Public Utilities Strike, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey: Racial Discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 5)
    - New Jersey: Schular - Religious Hatred Literature Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 6)
    - New Jersey: Traffic Workers Telephone Strike, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 7)
    - New Mexico: Shulman AVC Housing, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 8)
    - New York, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 9)
    - New York: Adams, Jeoffrey Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 10)
    - New York: Brackx Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 11)
    - New York: Canisius College Case - Separation of Church and State, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 12)
    - New York: Commission on Need for State University, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 13)
    - New York: Codon-Wadlin Bill - right of teachers to strike, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 14)
    - New York: Gallagher Union Discharge, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 15)
    - New York: Greene, Lancaster, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 16)
    - New York: Harris v. U.S., 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 17)
    - New York: Kemp v. Rubin - Restrictive Covenant Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 18)
    - New York: Mental Health, 1947; 1 folder (Box 561, Folder 19)
    - New York: NY State Committee for Equality in Education, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 1)
    - New York: Pakula, Wilson Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 2)
    - New York: People v. Scherer, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - New York: Reiter - American Legion Expulsion, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 4)
    - New York: Robeson, Paul - concert ban, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 5)
    - New York: State Committee Against Discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 6)
    - New York: United Electrical Workers Members Expulsion, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 7)
    - New York: U.S. v. Paramount Pictures, Inc., 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 8)
    - New York: Wilson-Concon Bill - Censor of movie ads, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 9)
    - New York: Winters Censorship Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Conscientious Objectors Freedom Train Picketing, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 11)
    - New York City: Health Dept. Regulations - Communicable Diseases, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 12)
    - New York City: Kane Fireman Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 13)
    - New York City: National Board of Review of Motion Pictures Conference, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 14)
    - New York City: Schapiro Search and Seizure Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 15)
    - New York City Committee, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 16)
    - New York City Committee: Advisory Council, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 17)
    - New York City Committee: Board Minutes, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 18)
    - New York City Committee: Academic Freedom Miscellaneous, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 19)
    - New York City Committee: Academic Freedom B.J. Stern Lecture Cancellations, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 20)
    - New York Committee: Academic Freedom Religious Practices in New York City School's Questionnaire, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 21)
    - New York Committee: Academic Freedom Timone Resolution, 1947; 1 folder (Box 562, Folder 22)
    - New York Committee: Arrests, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - New York Committee: Arrests Picketing Cases, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - New York Committee: Arrests Police Brutality, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 3)
    - New York Committee: City Council General, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 4)
    - New York Committee: Excessive Bail, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 5)
    - New York Committee: German-American Republican League - Meeting Hall Denials, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 6)
    - New York Committee: Legislature Miscellaneous, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 7)
    - New York Committee: Legislation Austin-Mahoney against Discrimination in Education, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 8)
    - New York Committee: Legislation Connelly Censorship Powers Bill, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 9)
    - New York Committee: Legislature Released Time for Religious Instruction Bill, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 10)
    - New York Committee: Legislature Shultz Amendment, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 11)
    - New York Committee: Medical Detention, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 12)
    - New York Committee: Racial Discrimination, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 13)
    - New York Committee: Racial Discrimination - Auditoriums in Housing Authority Projects, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 14)
    - New York Committee: Racial Discrimination - Dorsey et al v. Stuyvesant Town, Inc., 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 15)
    - New York Committee: Racial Discrimination - P.S. 169, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 16)
    - North Carolina, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 17)
    - Ohio, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 18)
    - Ohio: Scott, Clyde Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 19)
    - Ohio: Perkins v. Monroe, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 20)
    - Oregon: Namba - Alien Land Law Act, 1947; 1 folder (Box 563, Folder 21)
    - Oregon, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 2)
    - Rhode Island, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 3)
    - South Carolina: Earle Lynching, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 4)
    - South Carolina: White Primary, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 5)
    - South Dakota and Tennessee, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 6)
    - Texas, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 7)
    - Texas: Brannen Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 8)
    - Texas: Police Brutality of Lawyers, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 9)
    - Utah: Musser Polygamy Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 10)
    - Virginia, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 11)
    - Washington, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 12)
    - Washington: Boiler Makers, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 13)
    - Washington: Huey - Post Office Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 15)
    - Wisconsin: Lambert Case, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 16)
    - Wyoming, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 17)
    - Alabama, 1947; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 18)
    - Alabama: Boswell Amendment Test Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 19)
    - Alaska and Arizona, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 20)
    - Arizona: Kartus-Robles Legislative Expulsion, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 21)
    - Arkansas: Emigrant Labor Agent Statute, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 22)
    - California, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 23)
    - California: Amer, Kim Restrictive Covenant Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 24)
    - California: Chinese Immigration and Detention Cases, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 25)
    - California: Di Giorgio Ranch Strike, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 26)
    - California: Hardyman v. American Legion, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 27)
    - California: Jackson - Navy Worker Loyalty Dismissal Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 28)
    - California: McDermott, J. Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 29)
    - California: McGee, Michael Imprisonment, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 30)
    - California: Oyama et al State - Alien Land Law Act, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 31)
    - California: Perez-Davis Miscegenation Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 564, Folder 32)
    - California: Takahashi v. Fish and Game Commission, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - California: Turkington et al v. Municipal Court of San Francisco, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut: Hetzel Catholic Hospital Dismissal, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut: Inter-racial Commission, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut: Progressive Party Ballot Test, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut: Dr. Shupis Hospital Dismissal, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia: Galarza - School Segregation Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia: Restrictive Covenant Cases, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 10)
    - Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 11)
    - Illinois, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 12)
    - Illinois: McCollum Released Time Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 13)
    - Illinois: McDougall v. Greene - Ballot Law Test, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 14)
    - Illinois: Montgomery Ward Union Injunction, 1948; 1 folder (Box 565, Folder 15)
    - Indiana and Iowa, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Kansas, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 2)
    - Kansas: Lawrence - Restaurant Discrimination, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 3)
    - Kansas: Welch - Medication Detention Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 4)
    - Kentucky and Louisiana, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 6)
    - Maryland, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts: Barnes' Anti-Discrimination Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts: Galardi Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts: G.W. Hartman Libel Suit, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 10)
    - Michigan, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 11)
    - Michigan: Eisner Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 12)
    - Michigan: Lee, A. McClury Post Office Complaint, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 13)
    - Michigan: McLean, G. Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 14)
    - Michigan: Zarichny, J. Student Contempt Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 15)
    - Minnesota and Mississippi, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 16)
    - Missouri, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 17)
    - Missouri: Balaz - Released Time Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 18)
    - Missouri: Holloway Committment Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 19)
    - Montana, Nebraska, Nevada and New Hampshir, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 21)
    - New Jersey: Committee on Civil Liberties, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 22)
    - New Jersey: Everson School Bus Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 23)
    - New Jersey: Firearms Law, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 24)
    - New Jersey: Kovacs v. Cooper Sound Track Ordinance Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 25)
    - New Jersey: Longo, John Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 26)
    - New Jersey: Palisades Park Swimming Pool Discrimination Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 27)
    - New Jersey: Vaccination Test Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 566, Folder 28)
    - New Jersey: Borak, Henry - Pennsylvania Railroad Fingerprinting Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 1)
    - New York, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - New York: Buffalo Sound Track Ordinance, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - New York: Davis v. Atlantic Coast Line R.R. Company, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 4)
    - New York: Discrimination in Federal Reserve Bank Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 5)
    - New York: Election Law Ban on Convicted Conscientious Objectors, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 6)
    - New York: Ephlin, D.L. Attack Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 7)
    - New York: Full Salvation Union v. Portage Township (Mich.), 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 8)
    - New York: Gates, J. AVC Expulsion, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 9)
    - New York: Holderith Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 10)
    - New York: Kosenkina - Russian Political Asylum Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 11)
    - New York: O'Leary, Frank - Criminal Penal Law Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 12)
    - New York: Parker Collegiate Institute - Private School License Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 13)
    - New York: Purdue - Hack License Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 14)
    - New York: Saia v. NY - Lockport Sound Truck Decision, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 15)
    - New York: Shapiro v. U.S. Search and Seizure, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 16)
    - New York: Silverman-Barnett Loyalty Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 17)
    - New York City, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 18)
    - New York City: American Newspaper Guild Convention Resolutions, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Civil Liberties Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 20)
    - New York City: City Council, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Fair Housing Practices Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 22)
    - New York City: Freedom Train - American Heritage Foundation, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 23)
    - New York City: Harris - Street Preaching Permit Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 567, Folder 24)
    - New York City: Langston Hughes, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 1)
    - New York City: PAC Committee for Palestine, Inc. - Foreign Agents Registration, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Police Brutality, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 3)
    - New York City: Post Office Discrimination Against Women Cases, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Protest of Prime Minister Winston Churchill's Fulton, Missouri Speech, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 5)
    - New York City: Rosenthal v. Stichman - Beachhead Project Meeting Hall denied, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 6)
    - New York City: Socialist Workers Party Sound Truck Test, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 7)
    - New York City: State Committee Against Discrimination, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Stock Exchange Picketing, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Stone Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Thompson - Teacher Dismissal Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 11)
    - New York City: United Electrical Workers Anti-Communist Party Union Members Discharge Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 12)
    - North Carolina and North Dakota, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 13)
    - North Dakota: Mazakahomn, J.Conviction, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 14)
    - Ohio, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 15)
    - Ohio: McCartney - Prohibition Party Ballot Test, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 16)
    - Ohio: Oberlin College Civil Liberties Mock Convention, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 17)
    - Ohio: Socialist Party Ballot Test, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 18)
    - Oklahoma and Oregon, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania: Carmer, F.E. - Industrial Employment Review Board Loyalty Suspension, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania: Easton Sound Truck Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania: Van Natta Released Time Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 568, Folder 23)
    - Rhode Island and South Carolina, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - South Dakota: Jones - Married Teachers Discharge Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 3)
    - Texas, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Texas: Coleman - Mail Fraud Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 5)
    - Texas: Mexican School Children Segregation Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 6)
    - Utah, Vermont and Virginia, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 7)
    - Washington, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 8)
    - Washington: Conwell Un-American Activities Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 9)
    - Washington: Seattle Boilmakers Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 10)
    - West Virginia, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 11)
    - Wisconsin: Andreen - False Arrest Case, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 12)
    - Panama, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 13)
    - Puerto Rico: Civil Liberties Committee Proposal, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rico: University of Puerto Rico Student Strike, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 15)
    - Puerto Rico: Miscellaneous, 1948; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 16)
    - State Correspondence: General, 1949; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 17)
    - Alabama: Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 18)
    - Arizona: Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 19)
    - California: Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Box 569, Folder 20)
    - California: Alexander, et al v. U.S. - LA Communist Contempt Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 1)
    - California: Jones v. Horn - Restrictive Covenant, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 2)
    - California: Los Angeles County Civil Service Commission Listing of Authors League as Subversive, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut: Kovacs Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut: New Haven Board of Education ban on People's Party Meeting in School, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut: Westport Released Time Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 7)
    - Delaware, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia: Standard Airlines Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 10)
    - Florida, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 11)
    - Florida: Foxx - Arrest and Detention Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 12)
    - Florida: Knight, L.E. - Fraud Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 13)
    - Florida: Nottebaum Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 14)
    - Georgia, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 15)
    - Georgia: James, Jesse, Jr. - Due Process Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 16)
    - Georgia: Mallard - Murder Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 17)
    - Hawaii: Martial Law, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 18)
    - Hawaii: Stainback, et al v. Po, et al - Foreign Language Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 19)
    - Illinois, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 20)
    - Illinois: Chicago Race Riots, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 21)
    - Illinois: Marino v. Ragen (Habeas Corpus), 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 22)
    - Illinois: Ferminello v. City of Chicago - Free Speech Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 23)
    - Indiana, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 24)
    - Kansas, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 25)
    - Kansas: Gimpel: Nazi Saboteur - Espionage Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 26)
    - Kansas: Harris, G. - Forgery Conviction, 1949; 1 folder (Box 570, Folder 27)
    - Kentucky, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 1)
    - Louisiana, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 2)
    - Maine: Drunken Seamen Free Speech Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 3)
    - Maryland, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 4)
    - Maryland: Stanford - Oath of Office Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts: Summer - Postcard Obscenity Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 7)
    - Michigan, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 8)
    - Michigan: Detroit Municipal Employees Loyalty Oath Program, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 9)
    - Michigan: Detroit Newspapermen's Loyalty Certificates, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 10)
    - Michigan: Zarichny - Student Free Spech Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 11)
    - Missouri, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 12)
    - Missouri: Lewis, H.H. - Crank letters to Pearl S. Buck, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 13)
    - Missouri: McIntosh - Fair Trial Case, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 14)
    - Montana and New Hampshire, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey, 1949; 1 folder (Box 571, Folder 16)